http://www.coloradohome.org/privacy-policy

Call us: 303.832.2022
info@coloradohome.org
Facebook-f
Twitter
Why MH?
Menu
Why MH?
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, Rocky Mountain Home Association (RMHA) provides this Privacy Policy explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. All capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings assigned to them in the Terms and Conditions for use of the Website, located at https://www.coloradohome.org/terms-of-use. Those terms and conditions are to be read in conjunction with and are incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy.
The Information We Collect
The type of personally identifiable information that RMHA collects is the information directly provided to us by a User, including: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number,.The Website also allows you to submit information about other people and entities.RMHA may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit the Website, such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider.
How We Use the Information
RMHA may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for industry products listed or linked on our Website, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs, or services that we believe may be of interest to you.RMHA sometimes uses this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when we make changes to our Terms of Use or to contact you about a new program or services we are offering.RMHA uses the information that you provide to others to enable us to send them the relevant information which you have requested for them. From time to time, RMHA also may use this information to offer other products, programs, or services to them.RMHA sometimes uses the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our products, programs, and services and to enable us to provide a more tailored interface for individual Users.RMHA may disclose your personally identifiable information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request or legal process; for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena.Agents and contractors of RMHA who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for RMHA.Although RMHA takes appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, RMHA cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy or as otherwise permitted by law. Please see Section 5 of the Terms of Use.On occasion, RMHA may disclose personally identifiable information to companies whose practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy (e.g., marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you.RMHA may, on occasion, combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you.
Collection of information by third-party sites and sponsors
The Website may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different from ours. Users should consult the other sites’ privacy policies as RMHA has no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. Privacy choices you have made on a third-party site or platform will not apply to our use of the information we have collected directly. Our site contains links to other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any linked sites.The Website covered by this Privacy Policy may sometimes offer content which is co-branded with third parties (the “Co-Branded Content”). By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to use the Co-Branded Content. RMHA has no control over third party use of this information. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of the sites containing Co-Branded Content.RMHA may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at our Website. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad server may have collected from you. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any third-party ad sites.
Cookies
To enhance your experience with our Website, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or any other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our Website. However, once you choose to furnish personal information to the Website, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.RMHA uses cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our Website. For example, RMHA may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our Website). RMHA may also use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.
Our Commitment to Security
RMHA has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.
Effective Date and Amendments
This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 1, 2020. RMHA reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason. Amendments to this Privacy Policy will be posted to this site.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact us at:Rocky Mountain Home AssociationEagle Drive, #111Loveland, CO 80537
PO Box 1196, Berthoud, CO 80513
(303) 832-2022
info@coloradohome.org
Contact RMHA
Get in touch with us
Name
Email
Phone
Why manufactured homes?
Why manufactured homes?
Copyright © 2020 Rocky Mountain Home Association. All Rights Reserved. Powered by ManufacturedHomes.com
Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
